<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-2"?>
<root>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>You are in the room with a pool. Does the pool have something magical inside?</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>You have entered an empty room. To your left you see a mysterious door.</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>What is this room? Why are there 3 coffins in here?</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>Are those chains? Where the hell are you?</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>This must be a storage room.</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>This could be a storage room.</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>You have entered a mysterious room where the ground is broken. Could it contain a secret passage?</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>This room was someones bedroom. I wonder whose was it?</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>A workshop. What could you possibly find in a workshop? Maybe some useful tools are laying around.</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>Someone was playing poker on that table I guarantee it!</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>A room for the workers to sleep in. What is this a bunker?</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>Stairs that must lead somewhere.</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>Just an empty hallway.</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>There is a bunch of barrels around here. They must have something inside. Hopefully some ale</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>Stairs that must lead somewhere.</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>There are a bunch of barrels around. There must be something in them.</Soba>
    </Sobe>
	<Sobe>
        <Soba>Nalazite se u sobi sa bazenom. Ima li bazen nesto magicno u sebi?</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>Usli ste u praznu sobu. Na Vasoj lijevoj strani se nalaze vrate.</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>Kakva je ovo Soba? Zasto su ovdje 3 lijesa?</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>Jesu li to lanci? Gdje ste Vi to?</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>Ovo mora biti skladiste.</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>Ovo bi moglo biti skladiste.</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>Usli ste u misterioznu sobu s razbijenim tlom. Moze li sadrzavati tajni prolaz?</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>Ova je Soba bila necija spavaca Soba. Pitam se tko je to bio?</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>Ovo je radionica. Sto biste eventualno mogli pronaci u radionici? Mozda se ovdje nalaze neki alati</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>Netko je igrao poker za tim stolom, to jamcim!</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>Soba za spavanje radnika. Je li ovo bunker?</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>Stepenice koje moraju negdje voditi.</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>Samo prazan hodnik.</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>Ovdje ima gomila bacvi. Oni moraju imati nesto unutra. Nadam se pivi!</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>Stepenice koje moraju negdje voditi.</Soba>
    </Sobe>
    <Sobe>
        <Soba>Okolo je gomila bacvi. Mora nesto biti u njima.</Soba>
    </Sobe>
</root>